So I did a Smart Funny in Black show this week that was amazing with Jaleel White and
Wayne Brady, and I cannot thank them enough for just bringing their talents to the show.
But there was a moment in the show that really frustrated me because I very clearly state
that Smart Funny in Black is designed to be a safe space for Black folks to be our whole
Black selves, to exalt in Black innovation, et cetera.
And a part of that is also really illuminated in the interactiveness of the crowd.
So I start the show by saying, like, listen, we welcome everyone into this space, but
respect this place and know your place, which is, you know, make sure to participate.
Do not, like, draw attention to yourself.
Do not distract from what's going on here.
And there was a white woman in the front row who was just not participating.
Like, we do the electric slide in the show.
We sing happy birthday, the Stevie Wonder style in the show.
We do a moment of Ebony excellence.
Yeah.
She sat down for the electric slide.
I didn't see her singing for Stevie Wonder, and she would not do a moment of Ebony excellence.
And I called it out, and she was there with her brother, and I said, don't bring her back.
Because I called it out nicely at first, and then I gave context, and then she continued
to just be like, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
So I say all that to say, if you're coming to a Smart Funny in Black show and you don't
want to participate, please just sit in the back.
It is very distracting, and in this particular case, offensive.
Ba-dum-bum.
I'll see you in a second.
Bye-bye.